Guide to the Jazz Loft Project Records, 1950-2012 and undated RL.10001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Oral Histories, 1991-2010; 614 items
  - Charles, Teddy, 2002 June 27; Archival Resource Key; 14
    In this oral history, Charles discusses his musical upbringing and education at Juilliard, where he transitioned from playing piano and drums into playing the vibraphone. While at Juilliard, Charles met Hall Overton and worked closely with him in subsequent years, learning about Overton's ideas to develop complexity in the jazz sound by using combining composition and improvisation. Also discussed is the social and musical scene at Charles' apartment in New York City, frequented and shared by people like Miles Davis, Benny Goodman, and Gerry Mulligan.
    - Teddy Charles Transcripts, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Teddy Charles, 6/27/02, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2002 June 27 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0016)
    - Teddy Charles I, 6/27/02, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 27 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0009)
    - Teddy Charles II, 6/27/02, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 27 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0010)
    - Teddy Charles III, 6/27/02, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 27 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0011)
    - Teddy Charles IIIa, 6/27/02, Flower Dist., Bill Crow, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 27 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0012)
    - Teddy Charles, 6/27/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0014)
    - Teddy Charles, 1/3 or 4, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0015)
    - Teddy Charles, I, 6/27/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0016)
    - Teddy Charles, II, 6/27/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0017)
    - Teddy Charles, II, 6/27/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0018)
    - Teddy Charles, III, 6/27/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0019)
    - Teddy Charles, IV, 6/27/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0020)
    - Teddy Charles, 6/27/02, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2002 June 27 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0018)
  - Crow, Bill, 2002 June 29; Archival Resource Key; 15
    Bill Crow (b 1927) was born in Othello, WA. He learned to play piano as a child, and he played trumpet, baritone, and sousaphone through school. He began playing with jazz musicians and learned the bass. He frequently participated in Jazz Loft jam sessions with close friend Zoot Sims.
    In multiple interviews, Crow talks about his musical development and learning a range of instruments including valve trombone, drums, and saxophone, as well as his experiences playing in the Army, and his presence at the Jazz Loft. Crow also discusses working with players like Stan Getz, Zoot Sims, Al Haig and how being a part of the jazz scene drew him into writing.
    - Bill Crow Transcripts, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Bill Crow I, 6/29/02, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2002 June 29; 61 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0017)
    - Bill Crow II, 6/29/02, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2002 June 29; 58 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0018)
    - Bill Crow III, 6/29/02, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2002 June 29; 15 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0019)
    - Teddy Charles IIIa, 6/27/02, Flower Dist., Bill Crow, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 29 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0012)
    - Bill Crow I, 6/29/01, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 29 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0013)
    - Bill Crow II, 6/29/02, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 29 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0014)
    - Bill Crow III, 6/29/02, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2002 June 29 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0015)
    - Bill Crow, I, 6/29/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 29 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0021)
    - Bill Crow, II, 6/29/02, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2002 June 29 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0022)
    - Bill Crow, I, 6/29/02, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2002 June 29 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0019)
    - Bill Crow, II, 6-29-02, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2002 June 29 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0020)
    - Bill Crow, III, 6-29-02, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2002 June 29 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0021)
    - Sam Stephenson, Talk I., 8-11-04, Bill Crow, Dick Katz, Center for Jewish History, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 August 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0109)
    - Stephenson Talk Cont'd (II), Plus Bill Crow & Dick Katz, at Center for Jewish History, 8-11-04, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 August 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0110)
  - Cuber, Ronnie, 2000 October 26; Archival Resource Key; 16
    Ronnie Cuber (b 1941) was born in New York, NY. An alto saxophonist, Cuber took part in jam sessions with Chick Corea and others from 1963-64.
    In this oral history, Cuber discusses the culture of the Jazz Loft and its frequent visitors including Chick Corea, Henry Grimes, Lin Halliday, and Walter Davis. Cuber also talks briefly about his musical background playing in the Newport Youth Band, sitting in with Charlie Mingus at Birdland, and being a member of Maynard Ferguson's band.
    - Ronnie Cuber Transcripts, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Ronnie Cuber 10/26/00, Pete Yellin 10/28/00, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2000 October 26 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0020)
    - Ronnie Cuber, Pete Yellin, 10/00, Part 1, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2000 October 26 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0022)
    - Ronnie Cuber, 10/26/00, Pete Yellin, 10/28/00, Part 2, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2000 October 26 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0023)
  - Dante, Phil, 2004 November 09; Archival Resource Key; 17
    Phil Dante (1934-2004) was born in New York City. A photographer, Dante became the student and assistant of W. Eugene Smith between 1959 and 1961. He was also a founder of the photography collective En Foco. He traveled with Smith on assignment to photograph the Jack Daniels brewery in Tennessee.
    In this oral history, Dante describes his experiences working closely with W. Eugene Smith with particular attention paid to discussion of Smith's family background, his reliance on assistants, and his struggles with depression. Dante also talks about his own photography background and the controversy surrounding his reaction to works by Bruce Davidson.
    - Phil Dante Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Phil Dante 11/9/07 I, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 November 09 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0021)
    - Phil Dante, 11/9/04 II, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 November 09 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0022)
    - Phil Dante, 11/9/04 III, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 November 09; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0023)
    - Phil Dante I, 11/9/04, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 November 09 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0016)
    - Phil Dante 2/3, 11-9-04, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 November 09 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0017)
    - Phil Dante III/3, 11-9-04, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 November 09 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0018)
    - Phil Dante, I, 11/9/04, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2004 November 09 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0023)
    - Phil Dante, II, 11/9/04, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2004 November 09 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0024)
    - Phil Dante, III, 11/9/04, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2004 November 09 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0025)
    - Phil Dante, 11/9/04, I, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 November 09 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0024)
    - Phil Dante, 11/9/04, II, Part 1, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 November 09 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0025)
    - Phil Dante, 11/9/04, II, Part 2, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 November 09 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0026)
    - Phil Dante, III, 11/9/04, end of tape interview, (no need to transcribe "tape reels"), Some overlap from digital video (audio track), no need to paste repeated sections, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 November 09 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0027)
  - Davies, Dennis Russell, undated; 18
    Dennis Russell Davis (b 1944) is best known as a conductor and pianist. He conducted a performance of Hall Overton's opera "Huck Finn" in 1971 at Juilliard in New York City.
    - Untitled, digital audio tape, undated (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0143)
  - DeCelle, Bob, 2004 October 02; Archival Resource Key; 19
    Bob DeCelle (b 1925) was born in Roslindale, MA. A music copyist, DeCelle worked for Hall Overton and in the loft to write out scores for individual instrumentalists from Overton's charts for Thelonious Monk's big band concerts in 1959, 1963, and 1964.
    In this oral history, DeCelle talks about his musical development as a contract copyist and orchestra librarian for the New York Philharmonic. DeCelle also discusses Hall Overton at length, including Overton's work with Thelonious Monk on the arrangements for the Town Hall Concert and Overton's development of the Huck Finn opera.
    - Bob DeCelle Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Bob DeCelle I, 10/2/84, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 02 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0024)
    - Bob DeCelle II, 10/2/04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 02 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0025)
    - Bob DeCelle III, 10/2/04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 02 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0026)
    - Bob Decelle, 10-2-04, tape 1/3, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 02 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0019)
    - Bob Decelle, 10-2-04, tape 2/4, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 02 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0020)
    - Bob Decelle, 10-2-04, tape 3/4, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 02 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0021)
    - Bob Decelle, 10-2-04, Tape 4/4, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 02 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0022)
    - Bob DeCelle, I, 10/2/04, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2004 October 02 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0026)
    - Bob Decelle, II, 10/2/04, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2004 October 02 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0027)
    - Bob DeCelle, I, 10/2/04, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 02 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0028)
    - Bob DeCelle, II, 10/2/04, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 02 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0029)
    - Bob DeCelle, III, 10/2/04, & end of (II), Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 02 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0030)
  - Deloatch, Lois, 2007 August 22; 20
    Lois Deloatch is a jazz vocalist from Northampton County, NC. She holds degrees from UNC Chapel Hill and Duke University, where she served as associate director of corporate and foundation relations.
    - 8-22-07, Lois Deloatch, Sam Stephenson, Aaron Greenwald, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2007 August 22 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0027)
  - Duran, Manny, 2000 October 29; Archival Resource Key; 21
    Manny Duran (1926-2006) was born in Alamogordo, NM, where he began playing trumpet in mariachi bands. After discovering jazz, he moved to New York in 1956 and participated in many jam sessions during the Jazz Loft era.
    In this oral history, Duran talks about his life as a musician and his interaction with various musicians at the Jazz Loft including Lin Halliday, Zoot Sims, and Sonny Clarke. Duran also discusses the drug culture present in the Loft.
    - Manny Duran Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Eddie Bert 10-28-00, Roberta Arnold 10-29-00, Manny Duran 10-29-00, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2000 October 29 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0006)
    - Manny Duran, 1/11/06, II, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2000 October 29 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0029)
    - Manny Duran, 10-29-00, 1/1, NYC, w/S. Stephenson, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2000 October 29 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0028)
    - Roberta Arnold cont'd, 10-29-00, Manny Duran, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2000 October 29 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0010)
    - Manny Duran, 1/11/06, I, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2006 January 11 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0028)
    - Manny Duran, 1-11-06, NYC, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2006 January 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0023)
  - Early, Gerald, undated; 22
    Gerald Early (b 1952) is a scholar and educator whose primary foci are the study of jazz music, baseball, boxing, and African-American history.
    In this oral history, Early talks at length about the cultural, historical, and musicological importance of jazz as a truly American art form. Early discusses the rise of bebop, how the music of Thelonious Monk changed attitudes inside and outside of the jazz scene, and how the Jazz Loft recordings are important cultural artifacts.
    - Gerald Early Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Faller, Will, 2005 May 11; Archival Resource Key; 24
    Will Faller (b 1941) was born in Patterson, New Jersey. A photographer, Faller occasionally assisted Smith with printing photos. He gave Smith a Wollensak tape recorder, among other pieces of recording equipment.
    In this oral history, Faller discusses his relationship with W. Eugene Smith, particularly Smith's drinking and money issues. Faller also talks about his friendship with Charles Mingus, local New York City haunts of the time, and his professional work at Doyle Dane Bernbach.
    - Will Faller Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Will Faller, 5-11-05, I, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2005 May 11 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0030)
    - Will Fowler [sic], 5-11-05, II, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2005 May 11 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0031)
    - Will Faller, 05-11-05, I, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2005 May 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0024)
    - Will Faller, 5-11-05, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2005 May 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0025)
    - Will Faller, 5-11-05, I, cuts off at 1:02:20 (cont'd), Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2005 May 11 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0031)
    - Will Faller, 5-11-05, end of I, II, + DV tape from same interview, footage from end of DAT--> end, ~ 8 min., Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2005 May 11 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0032)
  - Feinstein, Harold, 2004 October 04; Archival Resource Key; 25
    Harold Feinstein (b 1931) was born in Coney Island, Brooklyn, NY and began taking photographs at age 15. He was an original loft resident from 1954 – 1957, when he turned it over to Gene Smith.
    In this photograph, Feinstein worked with Eugene Smith early on in his career, helping Smith edit and design the layouts for his famous Pittsburgh project. In this oral history, Feinstein discusses his work with Smith, his own development as a photographer, and about other people he encountered at the Jazz Loft including Sonny Rollins, Teddy Charles, Charles Mingus, and Dick Cary.
    - Harold Feinstein Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Harold Feinstein I, 10/4/04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 04; 59 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0032)
    - Harold Feinstein II, 10-4-04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 04; 59 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0033)
    - Harold Feinstein III, 10-4-04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 04; 9 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0034)
    - Harold Feinstein, 10-4-04, tape 1/3, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 04 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0026)
    - Harold Feinstein, 10-4-04, Tape 2/3, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 04 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0027)
    - Harold Feinstein, 10-4-04, Tape 3/3, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 04 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0028)
    - Harold Feinstein, 10-4-04, I, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 04 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0033)
    - Harold Feinstein, 10-4-04, II, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 04 (Box 25, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0034)
    - Harold Feinstein, 10-4-04, III, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 04 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0035)
  - Fetske, Ruth, 2004 October 01; Archival Resource Key; 26
    Ruth Fetske (b 1922) was born in Rahway, NJ. Fetske befriended Gene Smith while a student in a photography course he offered trough the New School. Fetske, an advertising account executive, enrolled in the course to develop her eye for editing photos for fashion ads. She looked after the loft while Smith was in Japan from September of 1961 to September of 1962, and she created a filing system to organize Smith's negatives, contact sheets, and prints.
    In this oral history, Fetske discusses how she studied with W. Eugene Smith at the New School and then went on to work as his assistant while Smith was living at the Jazz Loft. She also talks about learning techniques from Smith, her role in developing an organizational system for Smith's prints, and the variety of people that came and went in Smith's studio at the Loft.
    - Ruth Fetske Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Ruth Fetske I, 10/1/04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 01 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0035)
    - Ruth Fetske II, 10/1/04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 October 01 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0036)
    - Ruth Fetske, 10-1-04, tape 1/2, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 01 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0029)
    - Ruth Fetske, 10-1-04, Tape 2/2, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 October 01 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0030)
    - Ruth Fetske, 1/2, 10-01-04, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2004 October 01 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0029)
    - Ruth Fetske, 2/2, 10-01-04, Compact disc, Transcription copy, 2004 October 01 (Box 29, Audio-cd RL10001-CD-0030)
    - Ruth Fetske I, 10/1/04, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 01 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0036)
    - Ruth Fetske, I & II, 10/1/04, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 01 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0037)
    - Ruth Fetske, II, Part 2, 10/1/04, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 October 01 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0038)
  - Forscher, Marty, 2004 September 29; Archival Resource Key; 27
    Marty Forscher (1921-2009) was born in New York City. A legendary camera repairman, Forscher worked for Edward Steichen's Naval photographic unit during World War II before opening his own shop in New York called Professional Camera Repair. On a loft tape from 1960, saxophonist Zoot Sims expresses awe for Forscher's craft and dedication. Smith willed money to Forscher that he owed from many years earlier.
    In this oral history, Forscher talks about working as a camera repairman and inventor. He discusses how his interest in cameras developed, how he established his shop in New York City, and about some of the innovative devices and techniques he created. Forscher also talks about his work repairing cameras for people documenting the civil rights movement in the 1960's.
    - Marty Forscher Transcript, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Marty Forscher I, 9-29-04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 September 29 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0037)
    - Marty Forscher II, 9-29-04, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2004 September 29 (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0038)
    - Marty Forscher, 9-29-04, tape 1/3, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 September 29 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0031)
    - Marty Forscher, 9-29-04, tape 2/3, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 September 29 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0032)
    - Marty Forscher, 9-29-04, 3/3, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2004 September 29 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0033)
    - Marty Forscher, I, 9-29-04, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 September 29 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0039)
    - Marty Forscher, II, 9-29-04, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2004 September 29 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0040)
  - Free, Ron, 2003, 2006, 2008; 28
    Ron Free (b 1936) was born in Charleston, SC. Free began residency as loft house drummer in 1958, crashing on a recliner in Smith's loft until early 1960.
    In multiple interviews, Free talks about his upbringing, his first musical gigs in Charleston, S.C., and his life experiences at the Jazz Loft, particularly his time living with W. Eugene Smith Free. He also discusses his drug use, Smith's recording techniques, and his interactions with other musicians and personages at the Jazz Loft and in New York City including Woody Herman, Dave McKenna, Freddie Greenwell, and Pepper Adams.
    - 2006 May 10-11, Hot Springs, VA, Archival Resource Key
      - Transcript, 2006 May 10-11 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Ron Free, 5/10/06, I, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2006 May 10; 61 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0041)
      - Ron Free, 5/10/06, II, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2006 May 10; 64 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0042)
      - Ron Free, 5/11/06, I, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2006 May 11; 59 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0043)
      - Ron Free, 5/11/06, II, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2006 May 11; 62 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0044)
      - Ron Free, 5/11/06, III, Digital audio tape, Recorder original, 2006 May 11; 41 minutes (Box 19, Audio-cassette RL10001-DAT-0045)
      - Ron Free (Sam S., DanP.), 5-10-06, 1/5, Hot Springs, VA, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2006 May 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0034)
      - Ron Free, Hot Springs, VA, 5-10-06, Sam S./Dan P., Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2006 May 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0035)
      - Ron Free, Hot Springs, VA, 5-10-06 (Sam, Dan), 3/5, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2006 May 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0036)
      - Ron Free, Hot Springs, VA, 5-11-06, Sam, Dan, 4/5, Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2006 May 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0037)
      - Ron Free, Hot Springs, VA, 5-11-06, 5/5, Dan P., Sam S., Mini-dv videocassette, Recorder original, 2006 May 11 (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10001-MDV-0038)
      - Ron Free, 1/5, 5-10-06, Sam S., Dan P., Hot Springs, VA, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2006 May 11 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0042)
      - Ron Free, 2/5, 5-10-06, Hot Springs, VA, Sam, Dan, Standard Audio-cassette, Transcription copy, 2006 May 11 (Box 26, Audio-cassette RL10001-CS-0043)